Everyone you and I know
is hustling hard to survive the incoming
wave of AI,
yourself and even Declan here. Declan
is my editor,
but he's also running his own
business,
and you should probably be a bit worried
that AI is just going to take
everything that you do, do it better,
and put you out of a job before you're
even
25. Correct?
So now you're in a bit of a panic in your
life where you're like, "I need to make
money now or in the next three years,
or I'll never have the opportunity to use
my
skills to make money." He's nodding.
So in this video,
we're going to talk about how to operate a
one-man business,
because technically you're a one-man
business.
I was, for a long time,
a one-man business,
then I had to hire you to help me out
with stuff. But I became very profitable,
got a lot of green light signals early
on, built a brand,
and I didn't hire people till maybe six
years in.
So this video is for you.
It's also kind of for him,
and what's good is he's
probably going to ask me the questions
you're thinking of as we film it.
So running and operating a one-person
business is not difficult at
all. If anything, it's so much easier,
because managing people is just energy,
it's
organization,
and I think a lot of people
are saying to people,
"Oh, you should get someone to do this,
get someone to do that." No.
In the onset,
you want to do everything yourself.
You want to keep it tight-knit.
And also, the one thing that you
were asking me just before we started
recording,
Declan,
was about getting profitable early.
Now, as a one-man band,
you only need to cover your own bills.
If you come out the gates with staff,
you've got to pay a whole load of other
costs
before you actually get afloat.
I think it's also like you're probably
doing something else as your full-time
job,
so you need to find a way
that you can start making it somewhat
profitable early.
Yeah. And we're going to go through that.
So those of you that watched any of my
videos before, we've got a four-stage
framework,
and you can't jump steps on the framework.
The first one is socials,
then it's going to be squeeze,
then it's going to be
sell, then it's going to be scale.
We're going to go through
that downstairs in a
second. And in essence,
I'm going to teach you
that you don't need big teams, you
don't need to DM strangers,
you don't need to be doing sales calls-